classyauto.com 2016-10-15

# Privacy Policy

Home / Privacy Policy 

#### Effective as of May 1, 2004

National Vehicle takes your privacy seriously. We understand that privacy concerns are extremely important to our customers. We would like to assure you that we are committed to protecting your personal privacy and for that reason National Vehicle has created this privacy policy. Please read this Privacy Policy carefully so that you understand what information we collect through our website and what we do with that information

**Information We Collect**   
In order to ensure that consumers get the very best service, National Vehicle collects demographic information, web pages visited and other consumer-volunteered information from forms. National Vehicle’s request forms may require users to give us information such as your name, address, phone number, e-mail address and certain financial and credit-related information. Collected information is used to improve the content of our website, customize the content and/or layout of our website for individual users, and to contact users for marketing.

National Vehicle automatically receives and records information on our server logs from your browser, including your IP address, National Vehicle cookie information, and the page you request. We use information for the following general purposes: to customize content you see, fulfill your requests for products and services, improve our services, contact you, conduct research, and provide anonymous reporting for internal and external clients. 

**Children's Guidelines**  
Although this site is intended for the use of adults, and is not of likely interest to children, the forms on this site are capable of collecting online contact information from children who furnish it without prior parental consent or parental notification. Upon discovery that any such information may be supplied by children, such information shall be disregarded and deleted. 

**Cookies**  
Cookies are pieces of information that a web server may transfer to your computer through your web browser. When this information is stored on your computer, our system is able to recognize your browser and in turn customize web page content for you. We will not use any cookies to retrieve data from your hard drive or obtain sensitive information about you. When a cookie is set, your browser will check it for length, an expiration date, and where it originated. Only National Vehicle can access the cookies that we set. You can decide if and how your computer will accept a cookie by configuring your preferences or options in your browser. However, if you choose to reject cookies, you may not be able to use certain of our online services or website features. 

**Advertising**  
The ads appearing on this Web site are delivered to you by National Vehicle. Information about your visits to this site, such as number of times you have viewed an ad (but not your name, address, or other personal in-formation), is used to serve ads to you. 

**Security**  
National Vehicle understands the importance of security for our consumers. When applicable, we use the latest SSL (Secure Socket Layer) encryption technology to protect sensitive personal or financial information during transmission. This allows your personal information to be submitted in a secure environment while reaching the intended parties. An SSL-capable web browser is needed to support this encryption technology. Netscape Navigator 4.6 or higher or Microsoft’s Internet Explorer 4.01 or higher will support SSL technology. To verify that you are on a secure web page in Netscape Navigator, right-click while your cursor is on the form (not the border) and select “view Frame information” in Netscape Navigator. To view security certificates in Internet Explorer, click Internet Options on the View menu in the browser and then the Content tab. In the Certificates area, click the Personal, Sites, and Publishers buttons to view the current certificates. 

**Information We Share With Others**   
Only information used for the purpose of placing a classified ad is shared with other advertising partners.

If you have any questions about this policy please contact us at:

National Vehicle  
1941 S 42nd St, Suite 104  
Omaha NE 68105  
Toll-free at 1-800-320-9557  
Fax: 402-201-2663  
Local Phone: 402-342-1570

### Car Loan Resources

## Capital One Auto Finance

Hassle-free financing with great low rates. Get the flexibility to purchase your vehicle from an individual that currently has their vehicle financed, or from an individual that owns their vehicle outright.
